<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Biology on</title><link>https://heidihuang.dev/tags/Biology/</link><description>Recent content in Biology on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://heidihuang.dev/tags/Biology/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A Crack in Creation</title><link>https://heidihuang.dev/Books/A-Crack-in-Creation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://heidihuang.dev/Books/A-Crack-in-Creation/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Biology Stuff</title><link>https://heidihuang.dev/Biology/Biology-Stuff/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://heidihuang.dev/Biology/Biology-Stuff/</guid><description>Cool Papers [[Efficient genome editing in the mouse brain by local delivery of engineered Cas9 RNP complexes]] In vivo CRISPR base editing of PCSK9 durably lowers cholesterol in primates Engineering precision nanoparticles for drug delivery A traceless linker for aliphatic amines that rapidly and quantitatively fragments after reduction [[PDFs/A programmable dual RNA-guided DNA endonuclease in adaptive bacterial immunity|A programmable dual RNA-guided DNA endonuclease in adaptive bacterial immunity]] Books I&amp;rsquo;ve Read  [[Reading List|The Gene]] [[Reading List|The Code Breaker]] [[Books/For Blood and Money|For Blood and Money]] random stuff [[Glossary]] [[Journal/10-2023/What kind of research assistant do I want to be?</description></item><item><title>Cell culture tips</title><link>https://heidihuang.dev/Cell-culture-tips/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://heidihuang.dev/Cell-culture-tips/</guid><description>As my postdoc / mentor likes to say,
Trust no one
Tips Before each use Make sure sash is at the correct height Wipe down hood thoroughly with booze (70% ethanol) before starting and after each use Sterile handling Spray down everything that goes into the hood with booze, including First time putting your hands and arms into the hood: spray your gloved hands + a little bit up your sleeve Every time your hands exit the hood, spray them with booze again before putting them back into the hood Switch Pasteur pipette tips at at least between different cell types Apparently a controversial statement, but keep lids and caps facing up Avoid sucking up media into serological pipette gun Keep lids and caps on as often as possible Try your best to not touch the inside of dishes and flasks with pipettes and tips Organization Keep objects out of the vent at the front of the hood (push things inside the hood) Try not to pass hands, bottles, pipettes, tubes etc.</description></item><item><title>Flow Cytometry</title><link>https://heidihuang.dev/Biology/Flow-Cytometry/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://heidihuang.dev/Biology/Flow-Cytometry/</guid><description>Helpful animated video Takeaways from video Flow cytometry is an experimental technique used to count and analyze individual cells within a mixed population based on their size, shape, and other properties.</description></item><item><title>For Blood and Money</title><link>https://heidihuang.dev/Books/For-Blood-and-Money/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://heidihuang.dev/Books/For-Blood-and-Money/</guid><description>Overview Focuses on the biotech industry, billionaires, and the pursuit of blockbuster drugs. Explores the story of Acerta Pharma, Imbruvica, Calquence, and their role in revolutionizing blood cancer treatment.</description></item><item><title>Glossary</title><link>https://heidihuang.dev/Glossary/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://heidihuang.dev/Glossary/</guid><description> Lab techniques [[Biology/Flow Cytometry|Flow Cytometry]] [[Cell culture tips]]</description></item></channel></rss>